Guide to the Annette Weiner Papers MC 152
New York University Archives
- Series III: Field notes & Field works
  - Samoa- Samoa 1980 Tape 1, Side 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Samoa Notes- samoa Vocabulary on Marriage and funerals, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Samoa Notes- Samoan Vocabulary & Tribal Stories, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Trobriand Islands- Cricket & Comment on Trobriand's Cricket, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Trobriand Islands- Carving Prices List, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Trobriand Islands- Conclusion of Film of Journal of Daily Events- Book 1,2,3, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 1 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 2 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 3 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 4 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 5 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 6 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 7 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events-Personal & Professional Notes- Book 8 (On Film), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribe Inheritance and Land, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7826 5
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribe on Kinship, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribe on Kinship (continue), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribe on Kinship (Kin Terms), 1971, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribes on Magic, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribes on Magic (continue), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribes Vocabulary/ Language, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kitava Tribes Vocabulary/ Language (continue), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands- 'Milne Bay' Development Study, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands- 'Milne Bay District' Information Bulletins, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9A)
  - Trobriand Islands- Notes 'Villages", 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands- Original Hudson Test, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Residence Information, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Trobriand Islands- Transcribed Stories and Interviews, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book III, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book IV, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book V, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book VI, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book VII and VIII, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary from Malinowski, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary Notes, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Trobriand Islands- Word Tests: Emmanuel, Doyaguna, and Wilson, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Trobriand Islands- Art and Decoration of the Tribes, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7827 3
  - Trobriand Islands- Exchange Values- Gardens & Trade, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands- Geneology, Family, Laws and Behavior, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands- Homes and Residences of Tribesmen, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book I and II (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book III (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book IV (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book V (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book VI (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book VII (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal & Professional Notes- Book X (On Film), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language and Vocabulary of Tribes, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language and Vocabulary of Tribes (continue), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Trobriand Islands- Linda's Diary: Trip to Trobriand Islands, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Trobriand Islands- Magic Spells and Powerful Objects, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Trobriand Islands- Notebook from Journal of Daily Events- Book II and V, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Trobriand Islands- Personal Property & Taboo Objects, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Trobriand Islands- Property only for Inheritance-'Kula', 1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Trobriand Islands- Rituals of Mourning- 'Sogali", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Trobriand Islands- Sexual and Marriage Laws/ Rules, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Trobriand Islands- Story Telling & Teaching Practices, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Trobriand Islands- Symbolism and Vocabulary of Magic Practices, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Trobriand Islands- Transcribed Stories & Interviews, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Trobriand Islands- Warfare Between Tribes, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book I, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7828 1
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book II, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book III, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book IV, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book V, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book VI, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book VII, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book IX, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands- Vocabulary & Tribal Stories- Book X, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands- New Behavior- Cultural Assimilation & Outside Influences, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina Local Government Council Meeting Notes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Exchange and Trade Practices, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 2, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 3, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Trobriand Islands- Microfilm of Notes on Kiriwina Island Tribe, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Trobriand Islands- Transcribed Stories & Interviews, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Trobriand Islands- Tribal Interviews of the Kitava People, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 1, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 2, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 3, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 3, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 4, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe- Book 4 and Loose Notes, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Trobriand Islands- Language & Vocabulary of Kitava Tribe and Loose Notes, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Trobriand Islands- Map of Islands and Fieldnotes on Language, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Trobriand Islands- Milne Bay Map (Large one), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Trobriand Islands- PMB Manuscript No.41: Biga Boyowa, Baldwin, B: A Notional Study of the Trobriand Language, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Trobriand Islands- Copy of Fieldnotes- Kiriwina, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7829 9
  - Trobriand Islands- Hess, Michael: A History of the Milne Bay District Workers' Association, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands- Government Planning Meeting Notes, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands- Journal of Daily Events- Personal and Professional Notes, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina Local Council, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kwaibwaga Island Tribes, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands- Transcript from Film (Final Script of 'Disappearing World: The Trobriand Islands of Papua New Guinea'), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands- The Fieldwork Photographs of Jenness and Malinowski, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands- General Notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina/ Trobriand Islands Maps- Geographical and Tribal, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kula Ring Road, Noted by Peter, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Photos, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Trobriand Islands- Trobriand Islands from Encyclopedia, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Trobriand Islands- Notes and Vocabulary Cards, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Census Survey of Milne Bay District, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7830 7
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Household Survey, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Household Survey from 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Notebooks Reporting Census..., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- 1980 National Population Census Project: Circular to Users Availbility of Results and Census Code Lists (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- 1980 National Population Census Project: Milne Bay Province Census Report, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Census Report Documents- Records, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Census Report Documents- Records, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands Census- Household Census, by Tribes: Kwebarogatola, Katagava, Oilovau, etc..., undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands Kinship- Malinowski: Trobriand 'Kinship", 1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands Kinship- Vocabulary and Terminology of Kinship, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Malinowski Letter (Written by Annette Weiner), undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7831 5
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- The Class Systems of Kiriwinan Society, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Geneology of Tribal Families, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Geneology of Tribal Families, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Geneology of Tribal Families: Kinship Terminology, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Geneology: Kadesopi Family Trace, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Geneology: MuraSamsan Lapoli Family Trace, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Kiriwina Council, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Kiriwina Maps & Drawings, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Kiriwina Maps (Large Maps), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) I, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) II, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) III, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) IV, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) V, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Papers of Rev. Samuel Benjamin Fellows (1883-1900) VI, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Kiriwina Highschool, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Myth of Founding of Tribal Homeland, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Trobriand Islands- Kiriwina- Vocabulary & Language, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Book Reviews by various Authors (A-Z), 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7832 3
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Thomas Owen Beidelman (Articles & Book Reviews, dated from 1902-1974), undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Thomas Owen Beidelman (Articles & Book Reviews), 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Articles by various Authors (A-Z), undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Department of Social Sciences- University of Tokyo- Meeting of Anthropologists on Samoa and Trobriand Islands, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Granada Television- David Wason- Film Producer/ Director, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Granada Television Information on Anthropology Film & Trobriand Project, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Map of the Trobriand Islands- Pen and Ink, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Miscellaneous Notes (handwritten), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Newspaper Clippings on Trobriand Islands & Related Topics, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Personal Notebook (Field Journal) and mini-cassette, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Stories and Myths from Fieldnotes Interviews, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Tabalu Origin Myth, Collected & Correspondences on Origin Myth, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Travel Magazine- UK- Journal of Northern Business, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Trobriand Islander's Art & Totems, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Trobriand Islands' Film (Script, Letters, Periodicals), 1968-1989 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Letters from Trobriand Islanders (Personal Correspondence), 1976-1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- University of Papua New Guinea's Master Degree Program, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Fieldnotes& Miscellaneous- Miscellaneous Notes from Paris, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Series IV: Reprints
  This series contains Reprints articles related to her works and teaching. The files follow Alphabetical orders of either Name of the Articles or Authors, then Chronological orders.
  - NYU & Other- Acquisition List: University of Hawaii Library, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7833 1
  - NYU & Other- Acquisition List: University of Hawaii Library, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Acquisition List: University of Hawaii Library, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Acquisition List: University of Hawaii Library, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'A Native Community and Its Life-Style", undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7834 9
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'AIDS and Its Metaphors' by Sontag, Susan, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Behavior in Private Places...' by Emerson, Joan P, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Chapter 14: Seeing the AIDS Patient", 1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Cloth and Human Experience' edited by Schneider, J. and Weiner, Annette, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Complete Stories of the Great Ballets: Apollo' by Balanchine, George and Mason, Francis, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Dialectic of Enlightenment", 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Education and Special Interests", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Everything in Its Path' by Kai, T. Erikson, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- 1904 Article on 'Fashion' by Georg Simmel', undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Full Brother-Sister Marriage in Roman Egypt: Another Look", undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Power/ Knowledge", 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Article on Reproduction....., 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Shamanism, Colonialism: chapter 25, 27", 1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Social Theory and Practice: Narcissism, Femininity and Alienation", undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Stigma", undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Symbol and Privilege", undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Symbols in African Ritual' by Turner, Victor W., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Body in Pain: The Making and Unmaking of the World", undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Body Politic: The Defense of Sexual Restriction by Anti-Abortion Activists", undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Concept of Disease", 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Rhetoric of the Signified: the World of Fashion", undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'the Frailty of Authority: Royal Authority and Religious Legitimacy- Morocco's Elections", 1960-1984 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Limits of Genetic Inquiry", 1987 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Medicalization of American Society", 1986 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Mystery of Terpsichore", 1983 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Politics of Manopause: the Discovery of a Deficiency Disease", 1986 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'The Second Sex: part 6", undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Urban Archeology", 1979 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Visions of Excess' by Battaille, Georges, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - NYU & Other- Article on 'Woman in Sexist society: Beauty, Love, and Marriage", undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - NYU & Other- Appadurai, Arjun: C.V., Papers/ Letter to Annette Weiner, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7835 6
  - NYU & Other- Correspondence and Anthropology Papers sent to Annette Weiner, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Correspondence on Developing Program in History Department Program (Historical Archeology)-Letters, Course Outline, and Introduction, 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Correspondence about NYU Conferences and Events, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Documents on University Events (Anthropology Department) and Library Holdings, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Pacific Islands Nations Workshop- Reprinted Program, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Abele et al: The Incest Taboo and the Mating Patterns of Animals, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7836 4
  - NYU & Other- Anderson, Benedict R. O'G.: The Idea of Power in Javanese Culture, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Asad, Talal: Multiculturalism and British Identity in the Wake of the Rushdie Affair, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Asheri, David: Laws of Inheritance, Distribution of Land and Political Constitutions in Ancient Greece, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Atkinson, Jane Monnig: Review Essay "Anthropology", 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Baines, John: The Origins of Kinship in Egypt, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Barnes, J.A.: Physical and Social Kinship, 1961, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Baudelaire, Chorles: The Painter of Modern Life, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Beidelman, T.O.: Agonistic Exchange; Review of Clifford James; Swazi Royal Ritual, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- Benedict, Ruth: Anthropology and the Humanities, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Biesack, Aletta: Prolegomenon to Tongan Cultural History, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Boas, Franz: On Alternating Sounds; Race, Language, and Culture, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Boas, Franz: The Foundation of a National Anthropological Society; The American Ethnological Society, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Bohannan, Laura: A Geneological Charter, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - NYU & Other- Boon, James A.: Balinese Twins Times Two; Comparative Courtly Love, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Brown, K.C.: Hobbes Studies, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Burke, Peter: Sacred Rulers, Royal Priests: Rituals of the Early Modern Popes, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Carsten, Janet: Children in Between: Fostering and the Process of Kinship on Pulau Langkawi, Malaysia, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Cliffford, James: Introduction: Partial Truths; On Ethnographic Authority; Objects and Selves, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Cohn, Bernard S.: History and Anthropology, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Davenport, William: Nonunilinear Descent and Descent Groups; Social Organization, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Davies, John K.: Athenian Citicenship: the Descent Group and the Alternatives, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Diduk, Susan: Twins, Ancestors and Sosio-Economic change in Kedjom Society, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Douglas, Mary: The Self- Completing Animal, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Dummont, L.: Pure and Impure, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Eggan, Fred: Historical Changes in the Choctaw Kinship System; Social Anthropology; Kinship Introduction, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Evan-Pritchard, E.E.: The Intellectualist (Eng.) Interpretation of Magic; Interpretation of Magic; Science & Sentiment; Bruhl's Theory; A Zande Funeral Custom, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Firth, Raymond: A Note on Descent Groups in Polynesia; Primitive Art & Society, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7837 2
  - NYU & Other- Fischer, M.J. and Marcus, G.E.: Anthropology as Cultural Critique, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Fortes, Meyer: The Developmental Cycle in Domestic Groups: Introduction, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- The Subject and Power, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Freedman, Maurice: Family and Kinship in Chinese Society, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Freid, Morton H.: On the Evolution of Social Stratification and the State; The Classification of Corporate Unilineal, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Furet, Francois: Quantitative History, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Geerte, Clifford: Deep Play on the Balinese Cockfight; Religion As a Cultural System; Thick Description; Waddling In, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Ginsburg, Faye: Procreation Stories: Reproduction, Nurturance, and Procreation in Life Narratives of Abortion Activists, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- Goldwater, Robert: Art History and Anthropology: Some Comparisons of Methodology, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Goodenough, Ward H.: Residence Rules, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Goody, Jack: A Comparative Approach to Incest and Adultery, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Hallowell, A.I.: The History of Anthropology as an Anthropological Problem, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Hertz, Robert: Death...(correction), undated (Box 30, Folder 14)